http://www.aliiflowers.com/privacy-policy/

Alii Hawaiian Tropical FlowersShop Hawaiian Flowers & GiftsHawaiian FlowersHawaiian Flower AssortmentsLoose Orchid BlossomsFlowers of the MonthBlooming OrchidsBlooming Orchids of the MonthTropical Flowers by the DozenFoliageHawaiian Leis & CorsagesLeis Available 2020 COVID ShutdownFresh Flower LeisFragrant Hawaiian LeisGraduation LeisBlue LeisGreen LeisLavender LeisOrange LeisPurple LeisRed LeisWhite LeisYellow LeisBulk LeisVine and Leaf LeisLeis for MenHead, Wrist and Ankle LeisOrchid Corsages & BoutonnieresCandy Lei KitsHawaiian Gifts & Gift BasketsHawaiian Gift Baskets and BagsCandy Lei KitsHawaiian Spa GiftsHawaiian WeddingsLoose Orchid BlossomsHawaiian Wedding BouquetsOrchid Corsages & BoutonnieresHawaiian Wedding LeisHawaiian Wedding Favors and GiftsProducts w/ Free ShippingBlooming Orchids of the MonthBlooming OrchidsFlowers of the MonthSpecialsBlogContactAbout Alii FlowersContact Us – Questions?Call UsLinksCartMy AccountOrderingOrder Hawaiian Flower and Gifts – Ordering InformationSending Flowers from HawaiiHawaiian Flower, Lei and Orchid CareTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyFAQ866.528.2269
$0.00 0 item(s)No products in the cart.
$0.00 0 item(s)No products in the cart.
Alii Hawaiian Tropical FlowersShop Hawaiian Flowers & GiftsHawaiian FlowersHawaiian Flower AssortmentsLoose Orchid BlossomsFlowers of the MonthBlooming OrchidsBlooming Orchids of the MonthTropical Flowers by the DozenFoliageHawaiian Leis & CorsagesLeis Available 2020 COVID ShutdownFresh Flower LeisFragrant Hawaiian LeisGraduation LeisBlue LeisGreen LeisLavender LeisOrange LeisPurple LeisRed LeisWhite LeisYellow LeisBulk LeisVine and Leaf LeisLeis for MenHead, Wrist and Ankle LeisOrchid Corsages & BoutonnieresCandy Lei KitsHawaiian Gifts & Gift BasketsHawaiian Gift Baskets and BagsCandy Lei KitsHawaiian Spa GiftsHawaiian WeddingsLoose Orchid BlossomsHawaiian Wedding BouquetsOrchid Corsages & BoutonnieresHawaiian Wedding LeisHawaiian Wedding Favors and GiftsProducts w/ Free ShippingBlooming Orchids of the MonthBlooming OrchidsFlowers of the MonthSpecialsBlogContactAbout Alii FlowersContact Us – Questions?Call UsLinksCartMy AccountOrderingOrder Hawaiian Flower and Gifts – Ordering InformationSending Flowers from HawaiiHawaiian Flower, Lei and Orchid CareTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyFAQ866.528.2269 MenuNavigationAlii Hawaiian Tropical FlowersShop Hawaiian Flowers & GiftsHawaiian FlowersHawaiian Flower AssortmentsLoose Orchid BlossomsFlowers of the MonthBlooming OrchidsBlooming Orchids of the MonthTropical Flowers by the DozenFoliageHawaiian Leis & CorsagesLeis Available 2020 COVID ShutdownFresh Flower LeisFragrant Hawaiian LeisGraduation LeisBlue LeisGreen LeisLavender LeisOrange LeisPurple LeisRed LeisWhite LeisYellow LeisBulk LeisVine and Leaf LeisLeis for MenHead, Wrist and Ankle LeisOrchid Corsages & BoutonnieresCandy Lei KitsHawaiian Gifts & Gift BasketsHawaiian Gift Baskets and BagsCandy Lei KitsHawaiian Spa GiftsHawaiian WeddingsLoose Orchid BlossomsHawaiian Wedding BouquetsOrchid Corsages & BoutonnieresHawaiian Wedding LeisHawaiian Wedding Favors and GiftsProducts w/ Free ShippingBlooming Orchids of the MonthBlooming OrchidsFlowers of the MonthSpecialsBlogContactAbout Alii FlowersContact Us – Questions?Call UsLinksCartMy AccountOrderingOrder Hawaiian Flower and Gifts – Ordering InformationSending Flowers from HawaiiHawaiian Flower, Lei and Orchid CareTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyFAQ866.528.2269
Privacy Policy
When you send Hawaiian flowers we will never compromise your privacy, sell or rent your email address or any other personal information. We may email you with special offers from time to time but you can unsubscribe from our list if you do not wish to receive these emails.Out of respect for our customers, we will never include receipts or invoices in your Hawaiian gift shipments. We know it is completely inappropriate for us to send prices or brochures with your gifts, so we will never under any circumstances reveal the prices you have spent on any gift, and we will never market to your loved one, friend, relative, business associate, client, or recipient.When you check out of the secure shopping cart online, it will ask you for the recipient’s phone number. We will not under any circumstances other than to facilitate on time delivery, call the recipient. We include their telephone number as a courtesy to the courier, in case there is a problem with the address or if there is a problem delivering the package.We will not disclose the sender (our customer, you) on the package, so if you want the recipient to know who sent the package, please put your name on the gift card when you fill in the ‘gift note’ area of the shopping cart form.If your recipient does contact us and ask who sent the package, we will release the information unless you specifically request that we keep your order anonymous. There is a comments section in the checkout area for you to use.Registering with us at checkout will save you some time on future orders. We do not store credit card numbers or related information out of an abundance of caution to protect your financial data. You can join our mailing list to receive holiday specials, reminders, new products and coupon codes.Our order system does maintain all of the information provided when you place your order. The exception is your credit card information which is passed to our processor in a secure, encrypted manner. We are in full compliance with PCI security standards.The IP address of your computer is recorded when your order is placed. We do store this information as does our credit card processor. This helps with fraud prevention in the unlikely event someone in a remote location has access to your credit card information.We know that the foundation of our business is built upon customer referral, which depends upon outstanding customer service. We appreciate your business and want you to feel confident giving our name, number, or web site as a personal referral.
Coupons and SpecialsJoin Our Newsletter for Coupons and
Specials
Email:
Payment Methods
Online Payments
Copyright 2005-2020 Alii Hawaiian Tropical Flowers
